<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Henri Bergius]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Henri Bergius]]></description>
        <link>http://bergie.today/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 09:45:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://bergie.today/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Henri Bergius]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Henri Bergius</h1><p>Hacker and an occasional adventurer. Author of Create.js and NoFlo. Decoupling software, one piece at a time.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a8dbb119299a79ee58e74745948a85b944ce0704.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bergie.today/henri-bergius/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2b68871f-7afb-46c3-a8cd-ac5e3d68e126</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 03:55:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augmenting Human Intellect: A Conceptual Framework]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Augmenting Human Intellect: A Conceptual Framework</h1><p>By "augmenting human intellect" we mean increasing the capability of a man to approach a complex problem situation, to gain comprehension to suit his particular needs, and to derive solutions to problems. Increased capability in this respect is taken to mean a mixture of the following: more-rapid comprehension, better comprehension, the possibility of gaining a useful degree of comprehension in a situation that previously was too complex, speedier solutions, better solutions, and the possibility of finding solutions to problems that before seemed insoluble. And by "complex situations" we include the professional problems of diplomats, executives, social scientists, life scientists, physical scientists, attorneys, designers--whether the problem situation exists for twenty minutes or twenty years. We do not speak of isolated clever tricks that help in particular situations. We refer to a way of life in an integrated domain where hunches, cut-and-try, intangibles, and the human "feel for a situation" usefully co-exist with powerful concepts, streamlined terminology and notation, sophisticated methods, and high-powered electronic aids</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/34290f04e983355224cd1b0687d3af77608f237c.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.dougengelbart.org/pubs/augment-3906.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fc36d4c8-0fbf-43fc-a8a5-38436eb3cf8e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 09:45:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[This is the flying chainsaw drone you knew was coming]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>This is the flying chainsaw drone you knew was coming</h1><p>Truly, we live in a golden age of Putting Dangerous Things On Drones. We've seen people strap fireworks, paintball guns, real guns, and even flamethrowers to quadcopters and the like, and so it was only a matter of time before someone tried with power tools.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b16625ea5b5e5434b99c5139554cb557d062335e.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.theverge.com/2016/4/4/11359828/flying-chainsaw-drone-finland</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8e6d4b6a-ef78-41c4-9bb4-e917fecd6d43</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 13:27:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Panama Papers: Victims of Offshore]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Panama Papers: Victims of Offshore</h1><p>The Panama Papers is a global investigation into the sprawling, secretive industry of offshore that the world's rich and powerful use to hide assets and skirt rules by setting up front companies in far-flung jurisdictions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/14c3d6830db69cf7050227226ba2239f9edbb078.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F6XnH_OnpO0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4f712810-ad68-491c-b6aa-095835c51ca2</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:05:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hands-on with HoloLens: On the cusp of a revolution]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Hands-on with HoloLens: On the cusp of a revolution</h1><p>Since it was first revealed in Redmond at the start of last year, I've used HoloLens a couple more times. I did a development session that walked through developing a simple app for the headset using Unity, and I've also seen Microsoft's touring HoloLens experience that it was offering developers last year.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/37f5d84e95194bf1c29d3ac446e24cc20105805a.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2016/04/hands-on-hololens-on-the-cusp-of-a-revolution/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3c893ba3-2137-4560-aa5f-3784310d88e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Onboard Computer System]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Onboard Computer System</h1><p>A complete sailing navigation system / weather station / stereo system built on Raspberry Pi</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://perpetual.voyage/journal/1</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">959d06f1-3f49-4ef2-98a1-7979acd80090</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 08:35:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New Space Race]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The New Space Race</h1><p>Touting everything from asteroid mining to shoebox-sized satellites, a new generation of space entrepreneurs is taking the search for the next big thing to the farthest reaches of the galaxy</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8082c492ae0e426a0112378a8d1a2fcdeca82fa4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.alumni.hbs.edu/stories/Pages/story-impact.aspx?num=5152</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8e481ca2-a8f2-489f-9b15-ec94245882e8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 08:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing Safari Technology Preview]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Introducing Safari Technology Preview</h1><p>Starting today, there’s a new, convenient way to see what features and improvements are coming to Safari and other applications that use WebKit. Safari Technology Preview is a version of Safari for OS X, distributed by Apple, that includes a cutting-edge, in-development version of the WebKit browser engine. It’s a great way to test upcoming WebKit features and give feedback to the people building them when it’s most useful — early in development.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e4a1537ef515cf4c94f4b7c2980e6093a628b559.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://webkit.org/blog/6017/introducing-safari-technology-preview/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6d439508-fc62-46ee-929f-9509ea1b442a</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 14:33:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ubuntu on Windows -- The Ubuntu Userspace for Windows Developers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ubuntu on Windows -- The Ubuntu Userspace for Windows Developers</h1><p>I'm in San Francisco this week, attending Microsoft's Build developer conference, as a sponsored guest of Microsoft. That's perhaps a bit odd for me, as I hadn't used Windows in nearly 16 years. But that changed a few months ago, as I embarked on a super secret (and totally mind boggling!) project between Microsoft and Canonical, as unveiled today in a demo during Kevin Gallo's opening keynote of the Build conference....</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cc347c298a18bcb587bc60514611e3b537eda027.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.dustinkirkland.com/2016/03/ubuntu-on-windows.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9370a92e-914d-4672-9f63-abf73c25247d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 09:18:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When our culture's past is lost in the cloud]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>When our culture's past is lost in the cloud</h1><p>Imagine if the Declaration were composed today. It would almost certainly be written on a computer screen rather than with ink and paper, and the edits would be made electronically, through email exchanges or a file shared on the Internet. If we were lucky, a modern-day Jefferson would turn on track-changes and print copies of the document as it progressed. We’d at least know who wrote what, even if the generic computer type lacked the expressiveness of handwriting. More likely, the digital file would come to be erased or rendered unreadable by changes in technical standards. We’d have the words, but the document itself would have little resonance.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c478767a37610ab18f65ef1254f7c42fe0c775b7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/when-our-digital-memory-is-lost-in-the-cloud-what-becomes-of-our-human-history/2016/03/24/11ed1482-ba46-11e5-99f3-184bc379b12d_story.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dd0c840a-3837-47bf-9007-bbca157402eb</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 09:22:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>